# TOMÁS NAHUEL ANTELA RIZZO

JUNIOR FULLSTACK WEB DEVELOPER

# CONTACT

+34 638653950

tomasnahuelantela@gmail.com

tomhuel.xyz

Tomhuel

Tomás Nahuel Antela Rizzo

#### SKILLS

Team Work

Iniciative

Motivated

Fluid learning

**Effective Communication** 

Agiles Metodologies

#### RESIDENCE

Currently, I live in San Cristóbal de La Laguna, Canary Islands, but I'm always willing to venture into new places, even if it means changing my usual place of residence

I'm open to working remotely, in a hybrid setup, or in-person.

\_\_\_\_\_

#### EDUCATION

Advanced specific vocational training in Web Development

**IES Puerto de la Cruz** 

2021-2023

# LANGUAGES

English Intermediate
Spanish Native

#### ABOUT ME

Junior Full Stack Web Developer with experience on Laravel 8, Livewire, Javascript, etc. Interested in specialization on Backend, Python and IA's. Proactive and motivated to learn grow both personally and professionally.

I am interested in contributing and mutually benefiting with my colleagues and friends. Therefore, I am open to constructive proposals and opinions, aiming to generate a sense of comfort and trust in the people around me.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

# **FullStack Developer**

eAgora Algoritmo del Cambio

2023-2023

Period of training in Work Centers as FullStack Developer, focusing on Laravel 8 + Livewire + Bootstrap for Frontend development and Laravel Lumen + MySQL for Backend development.

#### Volunteer

Cerebritos\_ 2017-2023

I am volunteer with the Cerebritos\_ association, participating in various activities such as being a monitor for different workshops in the field of multiple intelligences, a monitor and coordinator at the Gamer Forum of Los Realejos, and various activities related to team management and/or events.

## **TECHNOLOGIES**

# Languages

HTML 5 CSS 3

PHP

Git

MySQL

JavaScript TypeScript

Java

# **Frameworks**

Laravel Livewire Angular Bootstrap 5

# **Interests**

Python (IA's)
Backend (REST, GraphQL, ...)
Django & FastAPI